cashfiesta.com 2006-10-18

# Make money online: Cashfiesta Policies

**We Respect Your Privacy**

We created this Privacy Policy in order to inform you about the information we collect on the Cashfiesta.com web site, how we use this information, how we protect it and what choices you have regarding the collection and use of your personal information. 

Please read the Privacy Policy carefully as by visiting and sharing information on the Cashfiesta.com site you agree to be bound by the Policy. 

**Information We Collect**

We collect two types of information: personally identifiable information that you expressly provide us with by enrolling as a Cashfiesta.com member and non-personally identifiable information. 

  * Personally Identifiable Information 

When you register as a member of Cashfiesta.com, you provide us with personally identifiable information such as name, e-mail address, physical address. For some promotions we may request a valid phone number. We may also request other personal information from you such as age, gender, birth year, education, annual household income, and interests. 

In addition, in order to send you checks valued $600 or more we may require that you provide financial information for tax purposes. 

Certain offers that appear on our site may require that you provide us with additional information, including financial information, so that we can in turn provide it to our partners who sponsor the offers. This partner-requested information will only be provided to the specific sponsor of the offer, and only if you request that offer. We will not use this information. 

  * Non-Personally Identifiable Information 

In addition to the personally identifiable information, we also collect certain information online arising from your use of the Cashfiesta.com program. This information is anonymous; it is not connected with your personal information. Types of non-personally identifiable information we may collect, not exhaustive: 

    * The URL that you came to our site from;
    * Your IP address at the time you visited our site;
    * Pages from our site you visited and time you spent at each page;
    * Number and type of offers you responded to.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small data files that a web site server stores on a computer. They contain information about activities performed by a user of the computer on the specific web site and characteristics of the computer at the time the user navigates the site. Examples: the IP address of the computer at the time the user navigates the site; the password the user has set for the site, so that the user doesn’t have to type it each time he/she tries to log in at the site, etc. As cookies are data files, not code, they cannot erase or read information from a computer’s hard drive or from other sites the computer user visits. Cookies can only be read by the server of the site, which has set them, so that information about activities on one site can’t be transferred through a cookie to another site. 

We may store two types of cookies on your computer: 

  * Session Cookies: These cookies are stored in the Internet browser and are deleted each time the browser is closed. We use session cookies mainly to facilitate site navigation: for example, once you log in to the site, you don’t have to log in again during the same session; and to personalize site experience.
  * Permanent Cookies: These cookies are stored on the hard drive of your computer. They are not exactly “permanent”. Each cookie has different “life span” determined by the web site that sets the cookie. We may use permanent cookies to store your username and password (encrypted) on your computer if you opt to have it saved.

We may use both types of cookies for aggregate audience analysis: where our visitors and members come from, which pages they visit, how much time they spend on the site, which offers are most popular among members, etc. No personal information is stored in the cookies. Note that if you disable cookies on your browser, your FiestaBar™ may not function properly and we may have difficulties rendering services to you. 

**Use of Your information**

We use your personal information to service the Cashfiesta.com program, communicate with you, fulfill your requests or process, validate and/or verify orders. For example, we need your mailing address in order to know where to send your monthly check. We use your e-mail address to send you our monthly newsletter and other transactional messages related to your Cashfiesta.com membership and, in case you opt to receive such, special offers and promotions from Cashfiesta.com and on behalf of our affiliated and non-affiliated partners. 

We use your non-personally identifiable information to facilitate and personalize your online experience and make it better. We also use non-personally identifiable information to compile information about our website users and their online behavior, to develop new features and services for the site, to track your experience on the site in order to show you only content and ads that we believe you may be interested in, and to analyze and prevent technical problems. 

**Disclosure**

Except as described below, personal information you provide through the Cashfiesta.com web site will not be shared with third parties without your permission. 

Some offers or services you choose to participate in may require us, by their terms, to forward your personal information (such as mailing address for delivery of orders) to a partner so that they can provide the service directly to you. If you become a member through a partner web site, your basic enrollment, activity and interest information may be shared with that partner, as applicable, and that partner may share information it collects about you with us, subject to its own privacy policies. We will provide you with notice of such instances at the point where the information is collected. 

We may also share your personal information with third party service providers that perform services on our behalf, such as: credit rating companies, email service providers, credit card processors. These companies can only use the information we provide for the purpose of providing you with the services you requested. 

If Cashfiesta.com or any of its assets are acquired by or merged with another entity, member information will be one of the transferred assets. 

Other circumstances under which we may disclose your personal information: (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (2) in the event you violate or breach an agreement with us; (3) in the event we believe you will harm the property or rights of Cashfiesta.com or those of Cashfiesta.com’s customers or affiliates, (4) in the event we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Cashfiesta.com terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

If you have opted to receive commercial messages from us and from our partners and no longer wish to receive those messages, you can opt out of receiving them by changing your communication preferences in the Edit Profile section of the site. However, your option not to receive commercial messages: (a) shall not preclude us from contacting you, by e-mail or otherwise, regarding your existing or past relationship with us (e.g. sending you updates about the Cashfiesta.com services, incl. our Monthly Bonus emails), and (b) shall not preclude us, including our employees, contractors, agents and other representatives, from accessing and viewing your personal information in the course of maintaining and improving the site. 

**Third Party Websites**

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Cashfiesta.com site. The site contains links that direct you to websites owned and operated by other companies. In particular, when you take advantage of an offer, you will be directed to a web site of our marketing partner that may also collect your personal information. Those web sites are beyond our control. You should read those sites' privacy policies before using them. If you wish to opt out of their mailings, you must do so through those sites. Third party ads that we run on our site may set cookies to measure advertising effectiveness and gather completely anonymous information. We have no access to or control over these cookies. Some of the Special Offers you have to complete in order to earn cash may also use cookies to track and report signups. If you have your cookies disabled, you may not receive credit for some offer signups. 

**Personal Information Updates**

You can modify or update your personal information after logging in to your Cashfiesta.com account and clicking on the Edit Profile link. 

**Security of Your Personal Information**

We secure your personal information by using reasonable technical efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of the information that we collect. Efforts we undertake to ensure the security of your data include but are not limited to: maintaining our own servers under our private control, data encryption and/or monitoring of our network and data for intrusions. However, perfect security does not exist on the internet. 

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Cashfiesta.com or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Cashfiesta.com site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

**No Information Collected from Children**

In compliance with the [Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)](http://www.coppa.org/coppa.htm) Cashfiesta.com will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If Cashfiesta.com obtains indication that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. 

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Starting from January 1, 2006, if you are a California resident, you have the right to receive: a) information identifying any third party company (ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for the company's direct marketing purposes; and b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information you must make a request in writing. Your request must include your name, registration email address, and a return address or it will not be processed. Such requests will not be processed more than once per calendar year. Requests made via email will not be accepted. Please mail your request to: Cashfiesta.com/ 41 Sutter St. # 1214/ San Francisco, CA 94104 

**Privacy Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. The new version will be posted on the site. Your continued use of the Cashfiesta.com site and its products/services represents your consent to the revised Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to periodically revisit the site for possible changes. 

**Contacting Us**

We value your trust and we are committed to your privacy. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, Cashfiesta.com practices, or feel that your privacy has been compromised in any way, please contact us at [support@cashfiesta.com](mailto:support@cashfiesta.com)
